カーズは ひきょうにも
影武者を戦わせ➡
Using Caesar 's bandana, Jojo barely defeated Wham.
自らは不意打ちで
背後から リサリサを刺し貫く！➡
リサリサと ジョジョは➡
絶体絶命のピンチに
追い込まれたのだった！〉
Next, Lisa Lisa faced off against Cars.
(ｼﾞｮｾﾌ)うお～‼ 貴様 カーズ！
どこまでも 腐り切ってやがる！
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)
《ジョジョは 知らないんだ｡➡
Stroheim and Speedwagon appeared suddenly with help.
あの女の人が
自分の母親であるということを》
♬～
However, in a cowardly turn, Cars used a double to fight.
He sprang out and stabbed Lisa Lisa in the back.
Jojo and Lisa Lisa are in the greatest peril of their lives!
くっ！
(ｶｰｽﾞ)落とすなよ ジョジョ｡➡
Cars, you bastard! I hope you rot in hell forever!
下は とがった水晶石の岩盤｡
落とせば 即死だ！
くっ… カーズ！
Jojo doesn 't know.
てめえの根性は➡
He doesn 't know that that woman is his own mother!
畑に捨てられ カビが生えて➡
ハエもたからねえ
カボチャみてえに➡
腐り切ってやがるぜ！
わめくがいい｡ ほざくがいい｡
ののしるがいい！
ロープを つかんでいる
貴様にできることは➡
それぐらいだからなあ｡
くっ！
Don't let go, Jojo.
It's a forest of crystal spikes below. She'd die instantly.
♬(ｵｰﾌﾟﾆﾝｸﾞﾃｰﾏ)
C-Cars!
Your soul is as rotten as a pumpkin left in a field that even flies won't visit!
♬ 静寂の底から
Shout at me. Grumble at me. Insult me.
♬ 目覚めるその柱たち 時を越え
While you're holding that rope, that's all you can really do.
♬ 深紅の血潮が
♬ 立ち上がる勇気を
♬ 惹きあわせる
Shijima no soko kara
From out of the stillness
♬ 受け継ぐ愛を 宿命と呼ぶなら
Timing:
Fadeout4
♬ 微笑む目で 次の手を
Mezameru sono hashira tachi
The Pillars of the past are awakening
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Toki wo koe
To the dawn of a new day
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Shinku no chishio ga
The river of crimson blood within you
♬ 闇を欺いて
刹那を躱して
Fadeout4
Typesetting:
♬ 刃すり抜け奴らの間隙を突け
Mazrim
Quality Check:
Tachiagaru yuuki wo hikiawaseru
Carries with it the courage to stand and fight
♬ つらぬいた信念が 未来を拓く
Uketsugu ai wo sadame to yobu nara
Even if the love I feel is just part of my legacy...
♬ Like a Bloody Storm
熱くLike a Bloody Stone
♬ 血脈に
刻まれた因縁に
Hohoemu me de tsugi no te wo
I'll still be smiling as I stay one step ahead
♬ 浮き上がる消えない誇りの絆
♬ 握りしめて
Yami wo azamuite setsuna wo kawashite
Defying the darkness and dodging death at every turn
Encoding:
Fadeout4
Yaiba surinuke yatsura no suki wo tsuke
Slipping past the knife's edge and striking when you least expect
Tsuranuita omoi ga mirai wo hiraku
The emotions running through me blaze a path to the future...
Raw Hunter: WRRRRY
Like a bloody storm
Atsuku like a bloody storm
Burning like a bloody storm
Ketsumyaku ni kizamareta innen ni
When the time comes to end the vendetta carried by our blood
Distro:
ExWizzard
Ukiagaru kienai hokori no kizuna
Remember that the bonds of pride will carry you through any storm
Nigirishimete
So hold them close
http://www.some-stuffs.com
Episode 24: "The Link to Jojo"
♬～
くっ… うう…｡
ああっ！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ･ｽﾓｰｷｰ)ああっ！
はあっ！
はぁ… はぁ…｡
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)ああっ…｡
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)ジョジョ… リサリサ！
Jojo! Lisa Lisa!
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)ジョジョは
自分が手にしているのが➡
Jojo doesn't realize his mother's life is in his hands!
母親の命だということを
知らない｡
Mr. Speedwagon, we should tell him!
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)スピードワゴンさん
教えてあげよう ジョジョに！
No.
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)いや…｡
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)どうして!?
Why not?!
今は そんなことより…｡
≪(爆発音)
It's not the time.
Stroheim, are you done with the vampires?!
シュトロハイム！
まだ 吸血鬼は片づかないのか!?➡
We have to help Jojo!
早く ジョジョを！
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)やかましィィィィ！➡
Give me a break!
これだけの数！➡
You think we can get rid of them in just a minute or two?!
１分や２分で
始末できるかァァァァ！
(吸血鬼たち)ぐああ～！
Get out of my sight!
くそっ！
邪魔だ 邪魔だァァァー！
ちィッ！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)駄目だ…➡
It's no good. They need more time!
シュトロハイムたちは
間に合わない！
ジョジョ…｡
Jojo...
ほ～ら 油断してると
ロープが下がるぞ｡
Careful, the rope will slip if you don't watch it.
ぐっ…｡
うりゃあああ！
あっ！
While you're holding the rope, your hasty feet can only move so far.
ロープがあっては
貴様の 癖の悪い足も➡
この程度の動きしか
できないなあ！
うぐっ… ああ～！
ああっ！
足が カーズに触れたのに➡
He kicked Cars, but the Ripple didn't flow into him!
波紋効果がない｡
W-We're in a real fix!
ぜ… 絶体絶命！
Looks like your Ripple is running dry.
その 相当 疲労している波紋｡
You might have just enough for one last, all-out attack.
死力を振り絞って あと一発
放てるかどうかと見たぞ｡
ぐっ…｡
このカーズは
このように ゆっくり近づき➡
I'll just stroll up to you and take your life like I'm plucking a flower.
花を摘むように
貴様の命を 刈り取るまで｡
はぁ… はぁ…｡
Cars!
カーズ！
ん？
It's true I might have barely enough in me for one final attack.
確かに 死力を振り絞っても➡
あと一発
放てるかどうかだろうよ｡
I'm not exactly confident.
自信がねえけどなあ！
ん？
But even so, I've come up with a plan.
だがな！
俺は 今 策を思いついた！
It's something to make you choke!
てめえを ギャフンと言わせる
策をなあ！
Do you want to know what it is?
知りたいか？ 知りたいか？
I won't tell you!
教えねえよ！
Hey!
(ｶｰｽﾞ)おい！
You're not tying any ropes together!
リサリサと 自分のロープを
結ぶんじゃあないぞ｡
(ｶｰｽﾞ)むっ!?
マッチの火だ！
This is a match!
What do you think I'll do with it?
この火を 俺は どうすると思う？
ふん｡
な… 何をやってるんだ？
ジョジョは｡➡
Wh-What is Jojo up to?
自分のマフラーに
火をつけてるぞ！
He set his scarf on fire!
Before this fire burns me, I'll use all I've got left to send you packing!
この火が 俺の体に燃え移る前に➡
てめえに あと一撃
振り絞った波紋を 食らわして➡
ぶっ倒してやる！
The fire is a gamble!
この火は賭けだ！
自分を追い込むための賭けだ！
It's a risk to motivate me!
I seek life within death!
｢死中の活｣ってやつよ！
ジョジョ そういうのをなあ…➡
Jojo...
An act like that...
ただの やけくそと言うのだ！
...reeks of desperation!
よっと！
(ｶｰｽﾞ)ふざけるなよ！➡
Don't toy with me.
You're just dodging around in order to catch your breath.
まず逃げ回って できるだけ
呼吸を回復しようとしているな？
I'll say it again: I want to kill you at my leisure.
もう一度 言う｡ 俺は楽をして
貴様を殺したいのだ！➡
I won't swing around like Tarzan!
ターザンごっこに
つきあってはおれん！
Come on, now! I need to breathe!
や～だよ！ まず呼吸だ！
Who cares if I look silly?
なりふり構ってられるか！
うっ…｡
いいか？
Listen.
俺は いつだって
この リサリサのロープを➡
I can cut Lisa Lisa's rope whenever I please.
切断できるのだぞ｡
今度 逃げ回ったら
即座に切断する！
And if you dodge again, I will!
ぐっ…｡
Is that all right?
(ｶｰｽﾞ)いいのか？
このロープを切っても｡
Should I cut the rope?
You want me to do it?
い･い･の･かあ～ぁ？
You don't, do you?
(ｶｰｽﾞ)困るだろう？
Don't!
やめろ！
(ｶｰｽﾞ)逃げた罰だ｡➡
You ran before. Now come to me, slowly.
今度は お前が ゆっくり
ここまで 近づいてこい｡
フッ…
ロープが 切れてもいいなら➡
If you want me to cut the rope, stay where you are.
近づいてこなくてもいいがな｡
くっ…｡
ひきょうな！
The coward!
What's your choice?
さあ どうする？
この女の命より
やっぱり 自分の方がかわいいか？
Is your life more precious than this woman's?
くっ…｡
うおお～っ！ 食らえっ！
Here's my choice!
I don't know what you're planning, but if I cut this, you'll fall as well!
何のつもりか 知らんが➡
このロープを切断すれば➡
自分も 一緒に落ちることに
気付かんのか｡➡
バカが～！
You fool!
Jojo!
ジョジョ！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)リサリサ！
Lisa Lisa!
フッ… バカめ！
これで 一石二鳥｡
Idiot. That's two birds with one cut.
むっ!?
What the...?!
何!? これは!?➡
He...!
このロープは ジョジョの足から!?
This rope is connected to Jojo!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ･ｽﾓｰｷｰ)おおっ！
When did he do it?!
一体 いつ結んだのだ!?
結ぶ余裕や
隙などなかったはず｡
He didn't have the time!
はっ！➡
最初の蹴りのとき➡
When he first kicked, he let himself be cut along with the rope!
わざと 足と一緒に
ロープを切らせ 余りを作ったな？
While he lit the match, he secretly tied his leg to her rope and made a loop.
その 余りのロープを
マッチをつけると見せ➡
リサリサのロープと 自分の足に
ひそかに結び 輪を作る｡➡
そして 自分の足元から
注意をそらすため➡
He needed a distraction.
So he set his scarf on fire.
わざと 自分のマフラーに
火を放ちおった！
And then to tie the ropes together, he let Lisa Lisa be cut down on purpose!
(ｶｰｽﾞ)おまけに
このロープの輪を 絡ませるため➡
わざと リサリサのロープを
切断させるように 挑発した！
That cunning devil!
こざかしいまねを！
Now you're holding me and Lisa Lisa up!
今度は お前が
俺とリサリサを 支えるんだな！
You deceived me, Jojo!
だましたな!? ジョジョ！
I never thought I'd hear that from you!
てめえから そんな言葉を聞くとは
思わなかったぜ！
だますのは得意だが
だまされるのは 苦手なようだな！
It seems you like tricking, but you hate to be tricked!
もっとも
１万年以上 生きてるらしいが➡
You may have lived for over 10,000 years.
But to compete with my skills, you need another decade!
俺とだまし比べで
張り合うには 10年早いぜ！
Cars!
カーズ！
SHAAHH！
食らえ！
Your time is up!
波紋！
Ripple Overdrive!
疾走！
はぁ… はぁ…｡
D-Did it work?
《き… 効いたか？》
T- That was the last of my Ripple.
《い… 今のが 最後の波紋だ｡
限界だぜ｡➡
I'm burned out.
Idon 't have any Ripple left.
もう これ以上
波紋は練れねえ…》
うう…｡
BAAHHHOHHHH！
I-It got into him!
な… 流れてたぜ！
Yes!
やった！
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)やったぞ！
He did it! He hit Cars with the Ripple!
カーズに 波紋を食らわした！
AAAHHH！
いよっと！
Off you go!
ぐおおっ！
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ･ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)おおおっ！
はぁ… はぁ…｡
(ｶｰｽﾞ)AH… AH…➡
ABAVVWWW…➡
AHHHOH…➡
お… のれ…｡
You...
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)おお～！ 見ろ！
Look! Cars fell into the crystal spikes!
カーズが
とがった水晶に落下した！
WKAKAKA…｡
ワッハッハッハー！
He's finished! See?
ついに やったぞ！
見ろ！ 波紋が あの野郎の腕を
どんどん上っていくぞ！➡
The Ripple will travel right up his arm!
You're weak! Your time is up!
弱っている！
もう 貴様は終わりだァァァー！
我々でも
とどめを刺せるぞォォーッ！
Even we could finish you now!
(兵士たち)お～！
(一同)うおっ！
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)
ふぅ… 脅かしおって…｡
He's trying to spook us.
All right! Let's eliminate him for good!
よ～し
ここは 確実にしとめたい！
Bring out the UV amplifier!
紫外線増幅装置を用意しろ！
(兵士たち)はっ！
Yes, sir!
はぁ… はぁ…｡
Master Lisa Lisa...
リサリサ先生…｡
はぁ… はぁ…｡
Cars said he didn't quite kill you.
カーズは 死なない程度に
生かしてあると言っていた｡
I don't think he hit anything vital.
急所は 外してあるはずだぜ…｡
はぁ… はぁ…｡
早く 手当てすりゃあ
きっと 死なずに済むだろうぜ…｡
If we act quickly, I'm sure you'll live through this.
ふぅ… ついに やった｡
It's finally over.
ああ… よかった｡
It is. I'm glad.
ねえ… スピードワゴンさん｡
Hey, Mr. Speedwagon?
ん？
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)１つ 聞いてもいいかい？
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
何だ？
Why did Granny Erina tell Jojo his mother died when he was little?
なぜ エリナおばあちゃんは
ジョジョに➡
｢母親は 小さいころに
病死した｣って言ってあるの？
うっ…｡
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)なぜ リサリサさんは➡
Why does Lisa Lisa hide her past from him?
ジョジョに 自分の全ての素性を
隠しているの？
Smokey, that's...
スモーキー それは…｡
Granny Erina told me not to ask you, but I have to know!
エリナおばあちゃんは
｢聞かないでほしい｣と言ったけど｡
でも 理由が知りたい！
She's his mother. Keeping that from him is awful.
実の親子なのに
隠してるなんて 悲しすぎるよ！
Smokey...
スモーキー…｡
Jojo and Granny Erina are my friends.
ジョジョと エリナおばあちゃんは
俺の友達だ｡
They saved me from crooked cops, even though I was just a thief.
ニューヨークで 悪徳ポリ公から➡
見ず知らずの ぬすっとの俺を
助けてくれた恩人なんだ｡
That's why I'm here! I'll do all I can to help.
だから ここまで ついてきた！
もし 何か 役に立てるなら！
ふぅ…
分かったよ スモーキー｡
All right, Smokey.
話してあげよう｡
I'll tell you.
You did take good care of Erina while I was away from New York, after all.
君は 私がいないニューヨークで➡
エリナさんの面倒を
よく見てくれたからな｡
でも
ジョジョには 決して言うな！
But promise not to tell Jojo!
This is a Joestar family issue. It's not our place to talk about it.
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
これは ジョースター家の問題で➡
我々が とやかく言うことでは
ないんだからな｡
リサリサというのは 仮の名前だ｡
The name "Lisa Lisa" is an alias.
彼女は
本名を エリザベスという｡
Her real name is Elizabeth.
She was raised by a Ripple-user named Straits.
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)ストレイツォという
波紋使いに育てられた彼女は…｡
She and Erina 's son, George, fell in love and got married.
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)エリナさんの息子
ジョージ･ジョースターと➡
恋に落ち 結婚した｡
(赤ん坊の泣き声)
George and Elizabeth had a son. You know him as Jojo.
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)ジョージと エリザベス
２人の間に生まれた子供｡➡
それが ジョジョだ｡
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
ジョジョの父親 ジョージは➡
Jojo 's father George was a member of the Royal Flying Corps.
イギリス空軍に所属する
軍人だった｡➡
第一次大戦中
飛行機は 急速に発展したが➡
A viation developed rapidly during the First World War.
ジョージは 初めて飛行機に乗った
勇気あるパイロットの１人で…｡
George was among the first brave pilots to fly into battle.
(機銃の音)
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)イギリス空軍でも➡
He stood out as a hero even among the Royal Flying Corps.
英雄とたたえられるほどの
男だった｡
However...
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)ところが！
... a gut-wrenching horror from the past came back to haunt the Joestars.
そこに 再び 過去の忌まわしい➡
どす黒い気分になる
因縁が浮上してきた｡➡
Fifty years before, a vampire named Dio had created a legion of blood-sucking zombies.
50年前 ディオという
男がつくった 吸血ゾンビたち｡➡
ストレイツォや 我々は
全てを退治し➡
Straits, myself and the others thought we had exterminated them.
全滅させたはずだったが➡
But one had escaped, hid within society, and lived for decades undiscovered!
１匹！ 我々から逃げ延び➡
社会に紛れて 数十年
隠れ潜んでいるやつがいた！➡
そのゾンビは こうかつで
頭のいいやつだった｡
This zombie was a cunning, intelligent creature.
(ｿﾞﾝﾋﾞのうめき声)
He created no spawn.
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
仲間を増やそうとはせず➡
He ate even the bones and hair of his victims, leaving no evidence.
自分が食らう人間は
骨も髪の毛も残さず 食らい➡
証拠が出ないようにしていた｡
And by some wicked twist of fate...
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
そのゾンビは こともあろうに！
... he worked as a commander in the Royal Flying Corps!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
イギリス空軍の司令官という
職に就いていたのだ！
T-The Royal Flying Corps? With Jojo's father?
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)イ… イギリス空軍!?➡
ジョジョのお父さんのいる？
That's right.
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)そうだ…➡
George uncovered his secret.
そのことに 気付いたのは
ジョージだった｡➡
He had listened well to Straits and me.
私や ストレイツォの話を
聞いていたからね｡➡
But ultimately, George was just an ordinary man.
しかし ジョージは
あくまで 普通の男｡➡
He had character and talent, but he hadn't trained with the Ripple.
資質と才能はあったのだが
波紋の修行をしていなかった！
(ｼﾞｮｰｼﾞ)《あっ！》
司令官の正体の 確証を得る前に➡
Before he could unmask the commander, he was discovered and attacked!
逆に 司令官に
悟られてしまったのだ！➡
そして ストレイツォへの連絡も
間に合わず…｡
His message to Straits wasn't in time.
(ｼﾞｮｰｼﾞ)《ぐわあっ！》
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)ジョージの死は➡
George's death was covered up as a nighttime plane crash.
夜間の飛行機事故に
見せかけられた｡
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)不審を抱いた
私とストレイツォが 調査し➡
Straits and I found this suspicious, and eventually found the truth.
事実を突き止めたのだが｡
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
幼いジョジョを あやしながら➡
That night, I told Elizabeth as she held an infant Jojo.
私の報告を聞いた その夜｡
Instead of showing grief...
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)悲しむより先に➡
... she flew out of the house!
エリザベスは
家を飛び出していた！
(ｿﾞﾝﾋﾞ司令官)《う… ああ…》
《HAHEEEEE！》
She was a genius with the Ripple, but her emotions consumed her!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
エリザベスは 波紋の達人！➡
しかし 冷静ではなかった｡
She was witnessed when she killed the commander.
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)司令官を殺した現場を
目撃されてしまったのだ｡
(兵士)《ひいいっ！》
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)軍は ゾンビや
波紋のことなど 何も知らない｡➡
The military didn't know about zombies or the Ripple.
善良で 優秀な人間である
司令官に対し➡
They concluded that Elizabeth had attacked their beloved commander, killed him, and burned his body.
エリザベスが 危害を加え
さらに➡
燃やして殺したと 決めつけた！➡
Soon she was known around the world as a murderer and national traitor.
たちまち エリザベスは
空軍司令官殺しの汚名と➡
国家反逆罪で
全世界へ 指名手配となったのだ！
♬～
We used all the Speedwagon Foundation's resources to cover her trail.
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
我々 スピードワゴン財団は➡
あらゆる手段で
エリザベスの身元を消し➡
彼女も黙って
イギリスを立ち去った｡➡
Elizabeth had to leave England behind...
我が子に 別れさえ告げずに｡
without even a word to her son.
(泣き声)
Erina knew what had happened, and she had a request.
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
その覚悟を知った エリナさんは➡
私に 静かに言った｡
(ｴﾘﾅ)
《このジョセフが 大きくなって➡
When this child grows up and asks about his parents...
両親のことを聞いたら➡
...please tell him they both died.
２人とも 死んだということに
してあげてください》
(ｴﾘﾅ)
《この子は… この子だけは…》
This child...
And so Elizabeth became Lisa Lisa.
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)そうして
彼女は リサリサになった｡
Why?
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)どうして…｡
Why is it that way?
どうして そんな…｡
お母さんは生きてる
ってことぐらい 教えても！
At least tell him his mother is alive!
I know painfully well why.
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
私には 痛いほど分かった！
えっ…｡
Erina lost her husband and son in the battle between the Ripple and the masks.
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)エリナさんは
息子と夫を失ったのだ！➡
石仮面と波紋を巡る 戦いで！➡
だから！
孫であるジョセフには➡
But thinking of her grandson Joseph... of Jojo...
ジョジョには！
...she didn't want the Ripple in his life!
波紋なんか知ってほしくないと
思っていたのだよ！
それは リサリサも同じだ！
Lisa Lisa felt the same way!
ううっ…｡
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)
《なんという 悲しい一族！➡
Such a tragic family.
ああ！
なんという 数奇な運命！》
Such a miserable fortune.
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)《でも 彼は➡
But now...
Now Jojo...
ジョジョは今！➡
Jojo used the Ripple to save his mother's life!
その波紋で！
自分の母親の命を 救ったんだ！》
あっ…｡
Mr. Speedwagon...
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)スピードワゴンさん｡
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)ん？
もう リサリサさんのことを
隠す必要はないよね？
Now there's no reason for Lisa Lisa to hide.
え…｡
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)ジョジョは➡
Jojo knows about the Ripple, and he used it to save his mother!
波紋を知ってしまったし➡
その波紋で
お母さんを助けたんだもの！
確かに…｡
True.
But it's not up to me.
だが わしの一存ではできん｡➡
We have to know how Erina and Lisa Lisa feel first.
エリナさんや リサリサの気持ちを
確かめなくては｡
そんな…｡
But...
Colonel!
≪(兵士)大佐！
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)えっ…｡
We're ready to fire!
(兵士)準備完了しました！
よ～し！
やつに狙いをつけろ！➡
Right! Aim it right at him!
このカーズは
我が軍が とどめを刺す！
We will have the honor of executing Cars!
(兵士たち)はっ！
ハハハハ！
Behold, Cars!
食らえィィィ！ カーズ！
貴様に とどめを刺せるなんて！
スカッとするぜ～！
I can't tell you how good it feels to give this order myself!
♬～
(一同)ああっ！
Don't, Stroheim! The mask!
やめろ！ シュトロハイム！
石仮面だ！
The Stone is in his mask! UV light will help him!
赤石が 石仮面にはまっているぞ！
紫外線はまずい！
D-Damn it!
や… やめい！ ストップだ！
Stop! Don't fire the UV amplifier!
紫外線を照射するなァー！
N-No!
し… しまった～！
♬～
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)あ… ああ…｡
し… 知らなかったんだ｡
I-I didn't see him holding the mask.
いつの間にか
石仮面を 隠し持っているなんて｡
I didn't see him put the Red Stone in!
赤石を はめちまっているなんて！
お… おお… 神様…｡
Dear God...
カーズ…｡
Cars...
♬～
♬(ｴﾝﾃﾞｨﾝｸﾞﾃｰﾏ)
♬ I'll be the roundabout
I'll be the roundabout
The words will make you out 'n' out
♬ The words
will make you out'n'out
We spend the day your way
♬ You spend the day away
♬ Call it morning
driving through
Call it morning driving through the sound and
♬ the sound and
in and out the valley
In and out the valley... hey!
♬ In and around the lake
In and around the lake
♬ Mountains come out of
the sky and they stand there
Mountains come out of the sky
and they stand there
♬ One mile over we'll be there
and we'll see you
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
♬ Ten true summers
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
♬ we'll be there
and laughing too
♬ Twenty four before
my love you'll see
Twenty four before my love you'll see I'll be
♬ I'll be there with you
there with you
♬～
Next Episode
The ultimate life form...
He can manipulate life at will!
Is there no way to stop him?
Cars, the Ultimate Being, is born!
Episode 25:
"Birth of the Ultimate Being"
(ｼｭﾄﾛﾊｲﾑ)究極の生物だと!?
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
やつは 生命を自由にできるのか!?
(ｽﾓｰｷｰ)もう あいつを倒すすべは
何もないのか…｡
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
究極の生命体カーズの誕生だ！